今天的课程是有关我们过去40年学到的创业知识
有趣的是，你们为什么学习这门课
I hope you're here to find out what does it take to go from an idea to a business.
我希望你们来这儿是为了学习如何把一个想法变成生意
For the last 20 years if you wanted to know how to go from an idea to a business,
在过去20年，若你想知道如何创业
the answer from educators and investors are simply, "Well, go research and then write
无论老师还是投资人答案都是：“那么，去做调研写份
a business plan and you'll know everything possible to actually start and run your business."
商业计划，然后你要学习所有创业和经营所需的知识”
We now know that advice was simply wrong--not kind of wrong but very wrong.
而我们现在明白，这种答案是错的，彻彻底底的错了。
We now today know something we didn't know before.
如今我们懂了过去不明白的地方
We now know the right way to build startups and so this class is about that right way,
我们现在知道了创业的正确路子，课程很快就会讲这个
but before we get started, let's see how we took the wrong path
不过在开始前，我们先看看错误的创业方法
and then see what we now know worse.
我们还会看更离谱的案例